Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1918-2011
  - Rebuilding America Conference (II), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Rebuilding America Conference, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Rebuilding New York Initiative, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - "Region's Cities: an Underground Report," by Peter Goldmark, Port Authority, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Regional Alliance for Small Contractors, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 70a)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Regional Plan News, Sep 1982 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Rent Stabilization Association, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - "Report of the Commission on the Year 2000", 1987 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Resource Recovery Program: New York City Sanitation, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Roofing and Waterproofing Contractors Association, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - St. John the Divine: Crane Purchase, Jul 1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Seelye Stevenson Value and Knecht, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Site Safety, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Site Safety, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Site Safety, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Society of the Plastics Industry, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - South Street Seaport (pamphlet), Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Special Report: "Virtual Design and Construction", 2008 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Speeches (Dandrow), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Speeches (John J. Collins), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Speeches (To Construction Finance Manager's Association), 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Staten Island Naval Base Homeport Project, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Steamfitting Industry Promotion Fund, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Steel Shortage, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Study of the New York City Building Code (Brooklyn Polytechnic), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Subcontractors Trade Association, 1984-1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Summit Meeting (Real Estate/Construction), Mar 1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Task Force on Capital Financing and Construction: Other "Three R's": Rebuilding, Renewing, and Reinvesting in the New York City Public Schools, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Taxpayer Action Lawsuit: Schulz v. State of New York, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Teacher Awards Luncheon (New York Alliance for the Public Schools), 1988 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Testimony (To New York State Division of Human Rights), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Testimony (To New York City Council, Committee on Economic Development, Louis Coletti), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Testimony (Richard T. Anderson), 1995-2009 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Testimony (Others), 1998-2006 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Traffic Congestion and Clean Air Act Requirements, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Trans Hudson Express Tunnel (pamphlet), circa 2006 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Truck Weight Study, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, Subcommittee on Economic Development, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Velez Organization, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Waste Disposal, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Waste Disposal Problem in New York City: Proposal for Action, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Waterfront Comprehensive Plan Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - West Side Highway Position Paper, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - West Side Transitway Planning and Feasibility Study: Working Papers, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Westway, Undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Westway: Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Westway: New York Citizens for Balanced Transportation, 1981-1986 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1976, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Westway: Public Notices, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Westway: Report by Kenneth Clark, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Westway: West Side Highway Replacement Study, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - "What's Happening on the Waterfront?" (Report, New York City Department of Ports and Terminals), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - "Wicks Law Reform", 1981 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Wolfe, Tom: From Bauhaus to Our House (Interview re:), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Zoning, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Zoning: Fifth Avenue, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Zoning: Second Avenue Subway, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Zoning: Special Transportation Districts, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Zoning Resolution: Proposed Amendments, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Zoning Resolution: Proposed Amendments, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Series IV: Events, 1938-2010
  Series IV: Events, 1938-2010 contains the records of the many events organized by the NYBC. The material on the Christmas shows and "Fun and Frolic" shows is particularly rich. There is also substantial material on the NYBC's 50th Anniversary celebration and the 1995 breakfast forums.
  - Anniversary (25th), 1938 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Anniversary (25th), 1946 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Anniversary (40th): General, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Anniversary (40th): Memos and Correspondence, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Anniversary (50th): Attendees and Seating Lists, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Anniversary (50th): Budget, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary (50th): Committee, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary (50th): Correspondence, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary (50th): General, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary (50th): Memos, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary (50th): New York Times Sunday Supplement, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary (50th): New York Times Sunday Supplement, Requests for, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary (50th): Speeches, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary (50th): Sponsors, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Anniversary (60th), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Anniversary (70th), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Anniversary (75th), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meetings, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meetings, 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Annual Meetings, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meetings, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meetings, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meetings, 2001-2010 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Breakfast Forum, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Breakfast Forum (Kaladjian), Jan 1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Breakfast Forum (Gelber), Feb 1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Breakfast Forum (Stasch), Mar 1995 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Breakfast Forum (Gargano), Apr 1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Breakfast Forum (Downs), May 1995 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Breakfast Forum (Powers, Schwartz), Jun 1995 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Breakfast Forum (Hevesi), Jul 1995 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Breakfast Forum (Membership Seminar), Sep 1995 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Breakfast Forum (Conway), Sep 1995 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Breakfast Forum (Vallone), Oct 1995 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Breakfast Forum (Hunter), Nov 1995 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Breakfast Forum (Ferrer), Dec 1995 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Breakfast Forum, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Breakfast Forum, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Breakfast Forum: Agendas, 2000-2010 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Breakfast Forum: Invitations, 2000-2007 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Breakfast with New York City Council, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Building Industry Forum, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Christmas Luncheon, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Christmas Show, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Christmas Show, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Christmas Show, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Show, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Show, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Show, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Show, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Show, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Show, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Show, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Show, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Show, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Show, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Christmas Show, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Show, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Show, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Show, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Christmas Show, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Show, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Christmas Show, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Christmas Show Titles (List) with Lyrics, 1938-1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller Candidates Meeting, Jul 2009 (Box 18, Folder 19a)
  - Conference: Business/Labor, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Conference: Contractors, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Conference: Energy, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Conference: Indoor Air Quality, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Conference: Rebuilding New York, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Conference: Rebuilding New York, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Conference: Smoke Toxicity, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Conference: Taiwan and New York/New Jersey Design and Construction Industry, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Conference: Urban Design, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Construction Industry Colloquium on Infrastructure, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Construction Industry Forecast Seminars, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Construction Industry Forum: Speaker, Host, and Venue List (2004-2011), 2010 (Box 18, Folder 30a)
  - Construction Industry Summits, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Dinkins-Stein Debate, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 1998-2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 10a)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition - Chairman and Guest(s) of Honor List (1996-2010) (Box 19, Folder 10b)
  - Dinner: Max Foley Jubilee, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Dinner: New York Building Foundation Premier Wine Dinner, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Event Schedules, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fun and Frolic: Cartoon Ad Winners, 1947-1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", General, Dec 1963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", Cartoon Book, Dec 1963 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", Costumes, Dec 1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", Script and Playbill, Dec 1963 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Cartoon Art, Dec 1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Costumes, Dec 1964 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", General, Dec 1964 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Rehearsal Memos, Dec 1964 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Script, Playbill, Dec 1964 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," Cartoon Book, Dec 1965 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," General, Dec 1965 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," Playbill, Dec 1965 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," Rehearsal Memos, Dec 1965 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Fun and Frolic: "This is the Year that was," General, Dec 1966 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Fun and Frolic: "This is the Year that was," Script and Playbill, Dec 1966 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1967 Show, General, Dec 1967 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Trouble is Building or Some Days are for Striking", Dec 1968 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Fun and Frolic: "No Nudes is Agnewds," General, Dec 1969 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Fun and Frolic: "A.ll F.or L.ove C.ash I.s O.ut or We Can Dream Can't We?", Dec 1970 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Fun and Frolic: 50th Anniversary Show, Mar 1971 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Fun and Frolic: 50th Anniversary Show, Script, Mar 1971 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Let Me Make it Perfectly Clear or HELP," Book, Dec 1972 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Let Me Make it Perfectly Clear or HELP," Script, Dec 1972 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Fun and Frolic: "The Man Who Came to Lunch," General, Dec 1973 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Oh What a Beautiful Morning or Cheers," Costumes, Dec 1974 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Oh What a Beautiful Morning or Cheers," General, Dec 1974 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Oh What a Beautiful Morning or Cheers," Script, Dec 1974 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1975 Show, Script, Dec 1975 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Up, Up or Oi Vey," General, Dec 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fun and Frolic: "We're Bouncing Back-You Too!!!", Script and Rehearsal Schedule, Dec 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1a)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Don't Look Back, Give the 80's a Whack," General, Dec 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1b)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1980 Show, Script, Dec 1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fun and Frolic: "How About You?", General, Dec 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fun and Frolic: "How About You?", Script, Dec 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fun and Frolic: 60th Anniversary Show, General, Mar 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fun and Frolic: 60th Anniversary Show, Program, Mar 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fun and Frolic: "All for Love or Cash is Out," General, Dec 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1983 Show, Script, Dec 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fun and Frolic: "No Endangered Species or Live in '85", Dec 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fun and Frolic: "No SNAFU or the Construction Connection", Dec 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Let Me Make it Perfectly Clear or HELP", Dec 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fun and Frolic: "'87 and Beyond or Let's Go B.C.", Dec 1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fun and Frolic: Unknown Show, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fundraiser for Brian McLaughlin, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fundraiser for Brian Steel, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "Future Development of the West Side Waterfront," Presentation by Michael Del Guidice, Oct 1990 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Holiday Show, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Holiday Show, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Show, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Holiday Show, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Housing Seminar, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Insurance Seminar, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Luncheon: City Club, Ed Koch Speaking, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Luncheon: Construction Industry, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon: Construction Industry, 2005-2010 (Box 20, Folder 24a)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Luncheon: Fall, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Luncheon Forum: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Luncheon Forum: Invitations, 2000-2007 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Luncheon: General, 1976-1996 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Luncheon: Governor Malcolm Wilson, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards (I), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards (II), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, Invitations and Responses, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2004-2006 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards - Chairman and Guest(s) of Honor List, 1995-2011 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Luncheon: Seating Lists, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon: Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Luncheon: Speakers List, 1926-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon with New York City Department of City Planning, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mayoral Candidates Forum, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Outing, Annual, 1978-1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Outing, Annual, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Outing, Annual, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Outing, Annual, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Outing, Annual, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Outing, Annual, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Outing, Annual, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Outing, Annual, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Outing, Annual, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Outing, Annual, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Outing, Annual, 2003-2008 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Outings: Game Rules, 1961-1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Pension Funds Investment Forum, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reception: General Charles E. Williams, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reception: Holiday, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reception: Joint Real Estate Industry (2nd Annual), 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Reception: Membership Reception, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Reception: Membership Reception, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Tour of New York Schools, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Series V: Oversized Materials, 1947-2008 (Box MSXOS002, Folder 1)
  Series V: Oversized Materials, 1947-2008 is comprised of oversized publications, ledgers, and other material.
  - Construction Industry Publicity Program Report, circa 1947 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Organization Chart (NYBC), 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - New York Construction News, Jan 14, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - New York Construction News: NYBC 65th Anniversary Supplement, May 19, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - New York Times: NYBC 50th Anniversary Advertising Supplement, Mar 28, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Organization Chart (NYBC), circa 1950s (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fun and Frolic: "'87 and Beyond or Let's Go B.C.," Sheet Music, Dec 1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Finances: Ledger, Cash Receipts, Jan 1949-May 1951, Apr 1953-Feb 1956 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Finances: Ledger, Events, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Building Congress Update, 1989, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - NYBC Update, 1992-2008 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Haines, Charles: Certificate of Life Membership, Jan 17, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Resolutions and Proclamations in Honor of the New York Building Congress, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Design for Certificates of Life Membership and Director Emeritus, Aug 31, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Certificate of Service: Stephen F. Voorhees, undated (Box MSXOS002, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1936-2008
  Series VI: Photographs
  The majority of photographic prints in the collection are black and white 8 x 10 prints; also included are color prints in a variety of sizes, including 4" x 6" and 3" x 4". Photographs and matching negatives are placed in the same folder, and the presence of negatives is noted in the finding aid. There are a limited number of contact sheets, also indicated in the finding aid. Additionally, this collection includes approximately 500 stereo slides dating from 1952 and 1953.
  Subseries VI:A: Meetings, 1947-1999, consists of photographs of administrative meetings, including those of the Board of Directors and Council of Presidents, as well as a variety of committees.
  Subseries VI:B: Events, 1944-2008, contains photographs of annual industry and social events, such as the Leadership Awards Luncheon, Fun and Frolic, the Industry Recognition Dinner, and golf outings. Also included are special receptions and forums with prominent visiting speakers.
  Subseries VI:C: Portraits, 1936-1988, includes portraits of key individuals in the building industry and political establishment in New York City. Many of these were acquired for use in NYBC publications, especially for publicity on featured speakers at Congress events.
  Subseries VI:D: Site Photographs, 1948-1974, contains a small number of photographs of construction sites and office environments.
  Subseries VI:E: Other Formats and Oversize, 1943-1988, contains stereo slides produced by the NYBC in 1952 and 1953. The approximately 500 stereo slides document meetings, the annual "Fun and Frolic" (1952 and 1953), and various social outings. Also included in this series are a small number of oversize items and the rolled photographs. Note that approximately 15 tightly rolled photographs, indicated as restricted in the finding aid, are not immediately available for reference use. Please consult Tamiment staff regarding access to these materials.
  - Suberies VI:A: Meetings, 1947-1999
    - Annual Meeting, May 21, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting (Hotel Astoria), May 5, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting (Grand Hyatt Hotel): Richard Green: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 20, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting (Includes Marilyn Gelber), 1994 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting: Breakfast Forum: Photos and Negatives, Jan 23, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, Jan 1999 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors; Membership and Building Industry Practices Committees, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors (Includes John Dyson), Mar 24, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors, Council of Presidents and Foundation Reception, May 1998 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors (Includes Tony Coles), Mar 24, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors: Prints and Negatives, Sep 19, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Board of Governors: Cocktail Party, Apr 27, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Board of Governors: Meeting: Presentation to Life Members, Mar 28, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Board of Governors: Meeting (Includes Marc Shaw and Stephan R.), Apr 1996 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Board of Governors and Council of Presidents Meeting: Negatives, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Board of Governors, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Capital Needs Assessment Meeting, Dec 11, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Committee: Economic Development and Energy: Joint Meeting with Con Edison, Feb 5, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Committee: Economic Development; Milos Riverso Forum; Public Buildings Committee: Prints and Negatives, Sep 1998 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Committee: Transportation: Prints and Negatives, Aug 1997 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Committee: Energy, Dec 1997 (Box 34, Folder 21)